<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog
                      http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-4.29.xsd"
        objectQuotingStrategy="QUOTE_ONLY_RESERVED_WORDS">
    <!-- John (user 1) already owns posts 1000-1009. Add ten posts for each of the other enabled,
         characteristic-profiled Keycloak accounts: Jane (2), Alice (4), Maya (7), and Theo (8).
         Of these forty posts, 28 have video, 6 have an image, and 6 are text-only: 70% / 15% / 15%. -->
    <changeSet id="0006-seed-active-account-posts" author="codex" context="seed">
        <sql splitStatements="true" stripComments="true"><![CDATA[
            INSERT INTO post
                (id, user_id, summary, support_question, case_for, case_against, is_unbiased, created_at, updated_at)
            VALUES
                (1010, 2,
                 'A city trial has cut bus fares to a flat two pounds for every journey. Passenger numbers rose quickly, but the subsidy is costing more than forecast and operators say crowded routes now need extra vehicles.',
                 'Should all local bus fares be capped at two pounds?',
                 'Simple low fares help households and tempt drivers out of cars.',
                 'A universal cap subsidises people who could pay and leaves less money for routes.', false,
                 '2026-07-02T09:00:00Z', '2026-07-02T09:00:00Z'),
                (1011, 2,
                 'Primary schools in one county now serve free breakfast to every child without asking families to prove their income. Teachers report calmer first lessons, while critics question paying for meals for affluent households.',
                 'Should every primary pupil receive a free school breakfast?',
                 'Universal provision removes stigma and ensures children start ready to learn.',
                 'Targeted support would direct limited money to families who need it most.', false,
                 '2026-07-03T09:00:00Z', '2026-07-03T09:00:00Z'),
                (1012, 2,
                 'A hospital is testing evening and weekend outpatient appointments to reduce its waiting list. Patients like the flexibility, but staff unions warn that extending hours without a larger workforce simply spreads exhaustion across the week.',
                 'Should routine hospital appointments run seven days a week?',
                 'Longer opening hours make care easier to reach and use expensive facilities fully.',
                 'Without more staff, seven-day clinics increase burnout rather than capacity.', false,
                 '2026-07-04T09:00:00Z', '2026-07-04T09:00:00Z'),
                (1013, 2,
                 'Supermarkets could soon be required to place clearer health warnings on foods high in salt, sugar, or saturated fat. Public-health teams expect better choices; producers say blunt labels flatten complex nutrition into a traffic light.',
                 'Should unhealthy food carry warning labels on the front of the pack?',
                 'Prominent warnings give shoppers useful information at the moment of choice.',
                 'Simple labels can mislead and punish products that are reasonable in moderation.', false,
                 '2026-07-05T09:00:00Z', '2026-07-05T09:00:00Z'),
                (1014, 2,
                 'Health teams are taking mobile vaccination clinics to shopping centres, workplaces, and transport hubs. Uptake has improved in underserved areas, though some doctors argue the programme duplicates services already available through local practices.',
                 'Should mobile vaccination clinics become a permanent service?',
                 'Bringing care to busy public places removes practical barriers to vaccination.',
                 'Permanent mobile teams may duplicate clinics and fragment patient records.', false,
                 '2026-07-06T09:00:00Z', '2026-07-06T09:00:00Z'),
                (1015, 2,
                 'Several employers are offering higher minimum pay for every hour worked overnight, not just a small shift allowance. Workers call it fair recognition of disrupted sleep; businesses warn that mandatory premiums would close marginal late-night services.',
                 'Should night workers be guaranteed a higher minimum wage?',
                 'Night work carries health and family costs that ordinary hourly pay ignores.',
                 'A mandatory premium could make useful round-the-clock services unaffordable.', false,
                 '2026-07-07T09:00:00Z', '2026-07-07T09:00:00Z'),
                (1016, 2,
                 'Pharmacists in a new pilot can diagnose and prescribe treatment for several common conditions without a GP appointment. The scheme is freeing doctor time, but patient groups want stronger safeguards when symptoms could signal something more serious.',
                 'Should pharmacists prescribe for more common illnesses?',
                 'Community pharmacies can treat routine problems quickly and relieve pressure on GPs.',
                 'Short consultations risk missing wider conditions that a doctor would investigate.', false,
                 '2026-07-08T09:00:00Z', '2026-07-08T09:00:00Z'),
                (1017, 2,
                 'A large employer now gives staff two paid mental-health days each year with no medical note required. Supporters say the policy prevents longer absences; sceptics say separate days are arbitrary and invite managers to judge which illnesses count.',
                 'Should workers receive dedicated paid mental-health days?',
                 'Early rest can stop stress becoming a longer and more serious absence.',
                 'One sick-leave policy should cover all health needs without creating special categories.', false,
                 '2026-07-09T09:00:00Z', '2026-07-09T09:00:00Z'),
                (1018, 2,
                 'Pollution sensors outside schools have recorded sharp peaks during the morning drop-off. The council wants temporary car-free streets at opening and closing times, while parents with long commutes say the plan ignores real family logistics.',
                 'Should streets outside schools close to cars at drop-off time?',
                 'School streets reduce dangerous traffic and the pollution children breathe.',
                 'Closures make difficult journeys harder for carers with limited alternatives.', false,
                 '2026-07-10T09:00:00Z', '2026-07-10T09:00:00Z'),
                (1019, 2,
                 'A proposal would give employees five paid days each year to care for an ill or disabled relative. Carers say emergencies cannot be scheduled as annual leave, but small employers fear the cost of covering unpredictable absences.',
                 'Should every worker receive paid carers leave?',
                 'Paid leave lets people handle family emergencies without losing income or work.',
                 'Small teams may struggle to fund and cover sudden additional absences.', false,
                 '2026-07-11T09:00:00Z', '2026-07-11T09:00:00Z'),

                (1020, 4,
                 'Universities are debating whether tuition fees should fall for courses delivered mostly online. Students point to reduced access to laboratories and campus facilities; institutions say teaching quality and staff costs do not shrink with the lecture room.',
                 'Should online university courses charge lower tuition fees?',
                 'Students should not pay the same when they receive fewer physical facilities.',
                 'Good teaching costs similar amounts whether it happens online or in a room.', false,
                 '2026-07-02T10:00:00Z', '2026-07-02T10:00:00Z'),
                (1021, 4,
                 'A research council wants data from publicly funded studies released within a year of publication. Open-data advocates say others can verify and reuse the work; researchers worry sensitive datasets will be misunderstood or stripped of context.',
                 'Should publicly funded research data be open by default?',
                 'Open data improves scrutiny and lets taxpayers gain more value from research.',
                 'Complex or sensitive datasets can cause harm when reused without expert context.', false,
                 '2026-07-03T10:00:00Z', '2026-07-03T10:00:00Z'),
                (1022, 4,
                 'The national science museum plans to remove entry charges for every special exhibition. Families welcome wider access, but trustees say ticket income currently pays for ambitious loans and installations that free admission may put at risk.',
                 'Should major science exhibitions always be free to enter?',
                 'Public museums should make important knowledge accessible regardless of income.',
                 'Ticket revenue funds exhibitions that public grants alone cannot support.', false,
                 '2026-07-04T10:00:00Z', '2026-07-04T10:00:00Z'),
                (1023, 4,
                 'Ministers are considering a ten-year research budget so laboratories can plan beyond annual spending rounds. Scientists say long horizons attract talent, while fiscal watchdogs warn that protected funding reduces room to respond when priorities change.',
                 'Should national research funding be guaranteed for ten years?',
                 'Stable budgets let long projects hire people and invest with confidence.',
                 'Future governments need flexibility to redirect money as national needs change.', false,
                 '2026-07-05T10:00:00Z', '2026-07-05T10:00:00Z'),
                (1024, 4,
                 'A group of universities will no longer count papers published behind expensive journal paywalls when assessing promotion. They want research available to everyone, but academics in specialist fields say prestigious closed journals still shape careers worldwide.',
                 'Should universities require researchers to publish open access?',
                 'Knowledge produced by universities should be available beyond wealthy institutions.',
                 'Strict mandates can limit where specialists publish and damage early careers.', false,
                 '2026-07-06T10:00:00Z', '2026-07-06T10:00:00Z'),
                (1025, 4,
                 'Plans for a new generation of small nuclear reactors promise steady low-carbon electricity from compact sites. Supporters see a partner for wind and solar; opponents point to unresolved waste, high financing costs, and a history of delayed projects.',
                 'Should the country invest in small modular nuclear reactors?',
                 'Reliable low-carbon generation can support the grid when renewable output falls.',
                 'Nuclear projects remain costly and leave waste burdens for future generations.', false,
                 '2026-07-07T10:00:00Z', '2026-07-07T10:00:00Z'),
                (1026, 4,
                 'The space agency is seeking extra funding for a domestic Earth-observation satellite. Scientists say it would improve climate and farming data; critics argue equivalent images can be bought from allies more cheaply than launching another national mission.',
                 'Should public money fund a new national Earth-observation satellite?',
                 'Independent observation capacity supports climate science, farming, and resilience.',
                 'Buying existing international data may deliver the same benefit for less money.', false,
                 '2026-07-08T10:00:00Z', '2026-07-08T10:00:00Z'),
                (1027, 4,
                 'Thousands of volunteers are measuring river quality with low-cost testing kits and publishing the results online. Their maps reveal pollution between official inspections, though regulators caution that inconsistent methods can create false alarms.',
                 'Should citizen-science data guide environmental enforcement?',
                 'Large volunteer networks can expose local problems that official sampling misses.',
                 'Enforcement decisions require consistent evidence collected to professional standards.', false,
                 '2026-07-09T10:00:00Z', '2026-07-09T10:00:00Z'),
                (1028, 4,
                 'Election officials want realistic AI-generated political videos to carry a permanent machine-readable label. Campaigners call it basic transparency; technologists warn that labels can be removed and may give unlabelled fakes a false air of authenticity.',
                 'Should political deepfakes be legally required to carry a label?',
                 'Clear disclosure helps voters distinguish persuasion from fabricated evidence.',
                 'Labels are easy to strip and may create misplaced trust in sophisticated fakes.', false,
                 '2026-07-10T10:00:00Z', '2026-07-10T10:00:00Z'),
                (1029, 4,
                 'A major journal is testing AI tools that flag statistical errors before human peer review. Editors say the checks catch routine mistakes quickly, while researchers worry opaque systems could quietly favour conventional methods and topics.',
                 'Should academic journals use AI to screen research papers?',
                 'Automated checks can catch common errors and free reviewers for deeper judgment.',
                 'Opaque screening may encode bias and reject unusual but valuable approaches.', false,
                 '2026-07-11T10:00:00Z', '2026-07-11T10:00:00Z'),

                (1030, 7,
                 'A council is considering limits on rent increases for existing tenants after another year of sharp rises. Renters want predictable housing costs; landlords say caps will push owners out of the market and reduce the supply of homes.',
                 'Should annual rent increases be capped?',
                 'Predictable increases protect tenants from sudden displacement and insecurity.',
                 'Caps can shrink rental supply and discourage maintenance and investment.', false,
                 '2026-07-02T11:00:00Z', '2026-07-02T11:00:00Z'),
                (1031, 7,
                 'Residents have formed a community land trust to buy an empty industrial site and build permanently affordable homes. The model keeps land outside the speculative market, but it relies on a substantial public loan and limits resale profits for buyers.',
                 'Should councils finance community land trusts?',
                 'Shared ownership of land can keep homes affordable for future generations.',
                 'Public loans carry risk and resale limits may deter would-be homeowners.', false,
                 '2026-07-03T11:00:00Z', '2026-07-03T11:00:00Z'),
                (1032, 7,
                 'The government is weighing thirty hours of free childcare each week from the end of parental leave. Families say the gap blocks parents from returning to work; nurseries warn the proposed hourly rate will not cover qualified staff and rising rent.',
                 'Should free childcare begin when parental leave ends?',
                 'Continuous support helps parents return to work and narrows early inequality.',
                 'An underfunded promise could close nurseries and reduce the quality of care.', false,
                 '2026-07-04T11:00:00Z', '2026-07-04T11:00:00Z'),
                (1033, 7,
                 'A protected cycle lane will replace parking along a busy shopping street. Transport planners expect safer journeys and more passing trade, while shopkeepers fear customers who buy bulky goods will simply drive elsewhere.',
                 'Should protected cycle lanes take priority over street parking?',
                 'Safe routes give more people a practical alternative to driving short distances.',
                 'Removing parking can hurt traders and people who cannot cycle or carry purchases.', false,
                 '2026-07-05T11:00:00Z', '2026-07-05T11:00:00Z'),
                (1034, 7,
                 'Libraries in one borough are staying open late with unstaffed access controlled by membership cards. Users value quiet evening study space, but librarians say unsupervised hours weaken safeguarding and turn a public service into a room with shelves.',
                 'Should libraries offer unstaffed late-night access?',
                 'Longer opening gives workers and students access when they can actually use it.',
                 'Libraries need trained people for safety, advice, and meaningful public service.', false,
                 '2026-07-06T11:00:00Z', '2026-07-06T11:00:00Z'),
                (1035, 7,
                 'Volunteer repair cafés are asking councils for permanent workshops where residents can fix appliances and learn practical skills. The projects cut waste, but commercial repair businesses say subsidised competitors may take away paying customers.',
                 'Should councils fund permanent community repair cafés?',
                 'Shared tools and skills keep useful products out of landfill and save money.',
                 'Publicly funded workshops may undercut local businesses offering the same service.', false,
                 '2026-07-07T11:00:00Z', '2026-07-07T11:00:00Z'),
                (1036, 7,
                 'Large restaurants could be required to publish how much edible food they throw away and set reduction targets. Campaigners say measurement drives action; owners argue waste varies with demand and public league tables would shame businesses facing unpredictable trade.',
                 'Should large food businesses publish their waste figures?',
                 'Transparent measurement creates pressure to prevent avoidable food waste.',
                 'Raw comparisons ignore business type and unpredictable day-to-day customer demand.', false,
                 '2026-07-08T11:00:00Z', '2026-07-08T11:00:00Z'),
                (1037, 7,
                 'A proposed rule would let asylum seekers work if their claim has not been decided within six months. Supporters say people should support themselves and fill vacancies; opponents fear work rights could encourage more people to make weak claims.',
                 'Should asylum seekers be allowed to work after six months?',
                 'Work provides independence, skills, tax revenue, and a route into community life.',
                 'Earlier access may complicate removals and create incentives for unfounded claims.', false,
                 '2026-07-09T11:00:00Z', '2026-07-09T11:00:00Z'),
                (1038, 7,
                 'The city has mapped large gaps between free public toilets, especially after early evening. A plan for staffed facilities would improve access and dignity, but councillors are divided over ongoing cleaning, security, and maintenance costs.',
                 'Should every town centre provide free staffed public toilets?',
                 'Reliable toilets make public space usable for older people, families, and disabled visitors.',
                 'Staffed facilities are expensive and can divert money from other local services.', false,
                 '2026-07-10T11:00:00Z', '2026-07-10T11:00:00Z'),
                (1039, 7,
                 'Rural councils want long-term national funding for bus routes that will never cover their costs through fares. Residents describe buses as essential infrastructure, while critics say flexible community transport may serve scattered populations more efficiently.',
                 'Should rural bus routes receive permanent public subsidy?',
                 'Reliable buses connect people to work, education, healthcare, and one another.',
                 'Fixed routes can be poor value where demand is low and widely dispersed.', false,
                 '2026-07-11T11:00:00Z', '2026-07-11T11:00:00Z'),

                (1040, 8,
                 'New power lines are needed to connect renewable generation, but proposed pylons cross several protected landscapes. Grid planners say delay will raise bills and waste clean power; residents want slower routes using underground cables.',
                 'Should new grid pylons be fast-tracked through planning?',
                 'Faster connections are essential to use new renewable power and cut costs.',
                 'National targets should not override landscapes and the communities living in them.', false,
                 '2026-07-02T12:00:00Z', '2026-07-02T12:00:00Z'),
                (1041, 8,
                 'A large offshore wind farm has won approval beyond a busy fishing ground. Developers promise clean power and port jobs, while fishing crews say turbine construction and exclusion zones threaten livelihoods built over generations.',
                 'Should offshore wind projects take priority over existing fishing grounds?',
                 'Large wind farms provide domestic clean energy and long-term coastal employment.',
                 'Fishing communities should not bear concentrated costs for a national policy.', false,
                 '2026-07-03T12:00:00Z', '2026-07-03T12:00:00Z'),
                (1042, 8,
                 'A grant scheme will cover most of the cost of heat pumps for lower-income homes. Engineers say the technology cuts emissions when buildings are properly insulated; installers warn rushed targets could leave households with unsuitable systems and high bills.',
                 'Should heat-pump grants focus first on lower-income households?',
                 'Targeted grants help people who cannot afford the transition or rising energy costs.',
                 'Means testing adds delay and may slow the growth of a skilled installation market.', false,
                 '2026-07-04T12:00:00Z', '2026-07-04T12:00:00Z'),
                (1043, 8,
                 'Drivers entering the most congested part of the city may soon pay a variable charge based on time of day. Economists expect faster journeys and cleaner air; opponents say workers with fixed hours will pay for a problem without gaining a realistic alternative.',
                 'Should cities charge drivers more at the busiest times?',
                 'Peak pricing cuts congestion and makes road users account for delays they create.',
                 'Charges fall hardest on workers whose hours and travel options are not flexible.', false,
                 '2026-07-05T12:00:00Z', '2026-07-05T12:00:00Z'),
                (1044, 8,
                 'The government is considering bringing passenger rail contracts into one public operator as they expire. Supporters want one accountable network; critics say removing competition risks slower innovation and hides poor performance inside a national monopoly.',
                 'Should passenger rail be run by a single public operator?',
                 'One network can coordinate fares, timetables, investment, and accountability.',
                 'A monopoly may weaken incentives to improve service and control costs.', false,
                 '2026-07-06T12:00:00Z', '2026-07-06T12:00:00Z'),
                (1045, 8,
                 'A broad carbon tax would replace several smaller environmental levies and return part of the revenue as a household dividend. Economists favour the clear price signal, but industries exposed to overseas competition fear production will move rather than decarbonise.',
                 'Should one economy-wide carbon tax replace existing green levies?',
                 'A predictable price rewards every practical way of cutting emissions.',
                 'Energy-intensive jobs may move abroad where producers face lower standards.', false,
                 '2026-07-07T12:00:00Z', '2026-07-07T12:00:00Z'),
                (1046, 8,
                 'Councils could be allowed to require landlords to insulate cold rental homes before raising rent. Tenants would gain lower bills, while landlords say older properties need costly work that rent controls could make impossible to finance.',
                 'Should landlords insulate homes before they can raise the rent?',
                 'Warm efficient homes reduce bills, illness, and wasted energy.',
                 'Upfront costs may force smaller landlords to sell or withdraw homes from rent.', false,
                 '2026-07-08T12:00:00Z', '2026-07-08T12:00:00Z'),
                (1047, 8,
                 'New petrol stations may be required to install rapid electric-vehicle chargers. Drivers want dependable coverage, but independent forecourts say grid upgrades and equipment costs could make already thin-margin sites unviable.',
                 'Should every large petrol station provide rapid EV charging?',
                 'A familiar nationwide network would make electric driving practical for more people.',
                 'Mandatory equipment may close rural and independent stations that cannot fund upgrades.', false,
                 '2026-07-09T12:00:00Z', '2026-07-09T12:00:00Z'),
                (1048, 8,
                 'Water companies want smart meters installed in every home to detect leaks and charge for actual use. Conservation groups support the change, while campaigners fear large families and people with medical needs could face unfairly high bills.',
                 'Should every household pay for the water it actually uses?',
                 'Metering rewards conservation and exposes costly leaks much sooner.',
                 'Essential water costs can rise unfairly for large households and medical users.', false,
                 '2026-07-10T12:00:00Z', '2026-07-10T12:00:00Z'),
                (1049, 8,
                 'Developers plan a grid-scale battery farm beside a village substation. The batteries would store renewable power and stabilise supply, but nearby residents want greater separation because of fire risk, construction traffic, and the industrial scale of the site.',
                 'Should battery farms receive priority planning near substations?',
                 'Storage close to grid connections reduces waste and supports reliable clean power.',
                 'Fast approval can leave nearby communities carrying safety and landscape risks.', false,
                 '2026-07-11T12:00:00Z', '2026-07-11T12:00:00Z');

            INSERT INTO post_media
                (id, post_id, media_type, orientation, s3_key, content_type, poster_s3_key, ordinal, created_at)
            VALUES
                -- Jane: 7 video, 2 image, 1 text-only (1019).
                (2110, 1010, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1010-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1010-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-02T09:00:00Z'),
                (2111, 1011, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1011-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1011-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-03T09:00:00Z'),
                (2112, 1012, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1012-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1012-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-04T09:00:00Z'),
                (2113, 1013, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1013-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1013-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-05T09:00:00Z'),
                (2114, 1014, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1014-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1014-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-06T09:00:00Z'),
                (2115, 1015, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1015-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1015-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-07T09:00:00Z'),
                (2116, 1016, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1016-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1016-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-08T09:00:00Z'),
                (2117, 1017, 'IMAGE', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1017-image.jpg', 'image/jpeg', NULL, 0, '2026-07-09T09:00:00Z'),
                (2118, 1018, 'IMAGE', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1018-image.jpg', 'image/jpeg', NULL, 0, '2026-07-10T09:00:00Z'),

                -- Alice: 7 video, 1 image, 2 text-only (1028-1029).
                (2120, 1020, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1020-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1020-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-02T10:00:00Z'),
                (2121, 1021, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1021-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1021-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-03T10:00:00Z'),
                (2122, 1022, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1022-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1022-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-04T10:00:00Z'),
                (2123, 1023, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1023-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1023-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-05T10:00:00Z'),
                (2124, 1024, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1024-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1024-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-06T10:00:00Z'),
                (2125, 1025, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1025-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1025-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-07T10:00:00Z'),
                (2126, 1026, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1026-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1026-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-08T10:00:00Z'),
                (2127, 1027, 'IMAGE', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1027-image.jpg', 'image/jpeg', NULL, 0, '2026-07-09T10:00:00Z'),

                -- Maya: 7 video, 2 image, 1 text-only (1039).
                (2130, 1030, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1030-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1030-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-02T11:00:00Z'),
                (2131, 1031, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1031-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1031-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-03T11:00:00Z'),
                (2132, 1032, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1032-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1032-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-04T11:00:00Z'),
                (2133, 1033, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1033-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1033-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-05T11:00:00Z'),
                (2134, 1034, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1034-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1034-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-06T11:00:00Z'),
                (2135, 1035, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1035-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1035-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-07T11:00:00Z'),
                (2136, 1036, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1036-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1036-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-08T11:00:00Z'),
                (2137, 1037, 'IMAGE', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1037-image.jpg', 'image/jpeg', NULL, 0, '2026-07-09T11:00:00Z'),
                (2138, 1038, 'IMAGE', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1038-image.jpg', 'image/jpeg', NULL, 0, '2026-07-10T11:00:00Z'),

                -- Theo: 7 video, 1 image, 2 text-only (1048-1049).
                (2140, 1040, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1040-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1040-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-02T12:00:00Z'),
                (2141, 1041, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1041-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1041-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-03T12:00:00Z'),
                (2142, 1042, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1042-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1042-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-04T12:00:00Z'),
                (2143, 1043, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1043-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1043-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-05T12:00:00Z'),
                (2144, 1044, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1044-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1044-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-06T12:00:00Z'),
                (2145, 1045, 'VIDEO', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1045-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1045-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-07T12:00:00Z'),
                (2146, 1046, 'VIDEO', 'PORTRAIT',  'posts/seed-1046-video.mp4', 'video/mp4', 'posts/seed-1046-poster.jpg', 0, '2026-07-08T12:00:00Z'),
                (2147, 1047, 'IMAGE', 'LANDSCAPE', 'posts/seed-1047-image.jpg', 'image/jpeg', NULL, 0, '2026-07-09T12:00:00Z');

            SELECT setval(pg_get_serial_sequence('post', 'id'), (SELECT MAX(id) FROM post));
            SELECT setval(pg_get_serial_sequence('post_media', 'id'), (SELECT MAX(id) FROM post_media));
        ]]></sql>
    </changeSet>
</databaseChangeLog>
